Alexander, Gabriel Arbitration Files 5133
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Ohio Power Co. - Pennsalt Chemicals Corp.. (Box 22)
  - Peerless Cement Co. -and- United Mine Workers of America, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Penberthy Mfg. Co. Div. of Buffalo-Eclipse Corp. -and- United Steelworkers of Amer. AFL-CIO, Local 2395, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Peninsular Metal Prod. Corp. -and- Local 189 - UAW, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Penn salt Chemical Corp. -and- Local 12100, Dist. 50 UMWA, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Penn Salt - UMW Grievance. 616, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Paramount Die Casting Co. -and- Local 2140, I.A.M., 1962 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Parke Davis - I.A.M., 1955 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Parke Davis - I.A.M., 1955 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Parker Wolverine, Div. of Udylite Corp. -and- UAW Local 189, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Ohio Power Co., 1961 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Ohio Power Co. -and- Utility Workers of America, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - The Olofsson Corp. -and- Local 724 UAW-CIO, 1962-1963 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Owens-Illinois Glass Co. Forest Prod. Div. -and- Local 994, UPP, AFL-CIO, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Palmer-Bee -and- United Steel Workers of America, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Palmer-Bee -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1959 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Paramount Die Casting Co. St. Jos. Mich. -and- Local 2140, I.A.M., 1961 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Pesco Div. of Borg-Wanrer - Rex Mfg. Co.. (Box 23)
  - Pennsalt Chem. Corp. -and- United Mine Workers Dist. 50, Local 12100 Grievance. 413-A, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Pesco Products Division Borg Warner Corp. (Bedford Heights, Ohio) -and- Local 363 UAW-CIO, 1956-1957 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Philco Corp. Mt. Clemens - IBEW, Local 1079, 1955-1959 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Phillips Petroleum. Co., 1952 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Pittsburgh Steel Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1962 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Warren Fisher Body-Engineering Center Contract (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Prophet Company -and- Local 1064 Retail and Wholesale Dept. Store Union, AFL-CIO, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Rainbo Bread Co. and United Dairy and Bakery Workers Local No. 87, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Rex Mfg. Co. (Aug. Grievances) -and- IUE, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Rex Mfg. Co. (Aug. Grievances ) -and- Local 919, IUE, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Rex Manufacturing Co. -and- Local, IUE, AFL-CIO, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Rex Manufacturing Company, 1958 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Rex Manufacturing Co., 1957-1959 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Rex Mfg. Co. - Sutherland Paper Co.. (Box 24)
  - Rex Manufacturing Co., 1957-1960 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Rowe A. C. Mfg. (Gr. Rapids) -and- Local 981, IUE-AFL-CIO, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Rowe AC Manufacturing -and- Local 981, IUE-AFL-CIO Grievance. No., 1964 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Ross Operating Valve Co. -and- Local 985, UAW-CIO, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - S.D. Warren Co. Central Mill -and- United Paperworkers of Amer. AFL-CIO, Local 1015, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Sealtest, Gr. Rapids Milk Branch -and- Local 386, United Dairy, Bakery and Food Workers, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Seneca Electric Co. -and- Dist. 60 I.A.M., 1958 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - South Buffalo Ry. - U.S.W.- C.I.O.-, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Square D. U.E. - Masterfile, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Standard Cotton Products., 1955 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Standard Cotton Products and UAW, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Standard Cotton Products -and- UAW, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Union Steel Products -and- Stovemounters AFL Local 67, 1954 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Standard Cotton Products Co. -and- Local 655 UAW, AFL-CIO, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Standard Cotton Products Co. -and- Local 655, UAW, AFL-CIO, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Strohs Brewing Co., 1959 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Sutherland Paper Co. -and- Local 1010 United Papermakers and Paperworkers of Amer. AFL-CIO, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Swift and Co. (1955-61). (Box 25)
  - Swift and Company, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Swift and Company, and Teamsters Cleveland Ohio, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Swift-Neuhoff. Nashville., 1955 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Swift and Co. -and- United Packinghouse Workers, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Swift and Company, Hastings, Nebraska Dairy and Poultry Plant, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Swift and Co. Denver (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Swift and Co. - Denver, Colo. -and- United Packinghouse Workers of America Local No., 1957 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Swift and Company Local 163 UPWA, CIO (Irene Perrotti), 1957 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Swift and Co. Discharge George Harmon, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Swift and Co. Little Rock, Ark. -and- Food Handlers Local 425 AMCBW of North America, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Swift and Co. St. Louis Plant -and- Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butchers Workmen of North America, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Swift and Co. Dairy and Poultry -and- Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butchers Workmen of North America AFL-CIO, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Swift and Co. United Packinghouse Works, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Swift and Co. (St. Paul, Minn) -and- Local 167 UPWA., 1957 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Swift and Co. Sales Unit - Chicago -and- Local 87, A.M.C. and B.W.N.A., 1958 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Swift and Co. Soybean Mill and Local 58 Amer. Federation of Grain Miller, AFL-CIO, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Swift and Co., Jackson, Miss. Dairy and Poultry Plant and Teamsters Union, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Swift and Company, Gainesville, Ga. -and- AMC and BW of North America, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Swift and Co. (Holiday Food Co.) Van Buren, Arkansas -and- Food Handlers Local 425 AMC and BW of Na., 1957 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Swift and Company (Boston) Grievance #392 Seniority Violation, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Swift and Co. Dairy and Poultry -and- Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butchers, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Swift and Co. (1955-61). (Box 26)
  - Swift and Co. -and- New England Dressed Meat and Wool Co., 1958 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Swift and Co. (St. Paul, Minn.) -and- United Packinghouse Works Arb. 325, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Swift and Co. (St. Paul, Minn.) -and- United Packinghouse Workers Arb. 326, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Swift and Co. -and- united Packinghouse Workers Arb. 328, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Swift and Co. (St. Paul, Minn.) -and- United Packing House Workers Local No., 1958 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Swift and co. (St. Paul, Minn) -and- United Packinghouse Workers Arb. 327, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Swift and Company -and- (Atlanta, Georgia), 1956 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Swift and Company -and- AMC and BW, 1957-1959 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Swift and Co. (Miami, Fla.) and Florida Sales Unit, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Swift and Company -and- AMCBW Gr. 527, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Swift and Co. Dairy and Poultry Plant (Jackson, Miss) -and- Local 527, AMCBW of NA, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Swift and Co. dairy and Poultry Plant (Nashville, Tenn.) -and- Local 405 AMCBW of NA, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Swift and Company -and- Meat Cutters, Packinghouse and Allied Food Workers Local 433 (Savannah, Ga.), 1958 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Swift and Co. -and- UPWA (Various Plants), 1959 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Swift and Co. -and- Local 522, AMCBW of NA (Moultrie, Georgia), 1959 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Swift and Co. (E. St. Louis) -and- AMCB of NA, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Swift and Company (Chambersburg, Pa) -and- Local 424 AMCBW, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Swift and Co. (Los Angeles) -and- Local 200 UPWA, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Swift and Company (Denver) and UPWA, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Tannevitz Co. - U.S. Industrial Chemicals Div.. (Box 27)
  - Tannewitz Company -and- I.A.M. Lodge No. 475, 1961 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Traffic Transport, Inc. -and- Shopmen's Local No. 508, International Association of Bridge, etc. Iron Workers, AFL-CIO, 1956 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Local 392, AFL-CIO, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Trane Company (Lacrosse, Wisc.) -and- I.A.M., 1958 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Trilex Corp. (Wayne, Mich.) -and- Local 985, UAW, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Union Trustees -and- Employer Trustees, Elec. Workers Pension Trust Funds of Local Union 58, IBEW, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - United Airlines grievance. 23010 I.A.M., 1960 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - United Air Lines -and- Air Line Dispatchers Assn., 1962 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - United Airlines Gr. 25788- Cleveland -and- District 141, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - United Air Lines -and- IAM - Dist. 141, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - United Air Lines -and- Air Line Dispatchers Assn. (Gay) Docket 63-1, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - United Air Lines (26695-IDL -and- IAM, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - United Air Lines (26760, 25647, 26718 IDL) -and- IAM System Board Cases, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - United Air Lines -and- Flight Dispatchers System Board of Adjustment Gr., 1958 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - U.S. Industrial Chem. Co. Div. National Distillers Prod. Corp. -and- Oil chem. And Atomic Workers International Union 509, 1957 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- U.S. Industrial Chemical Co. - Vickers Inc.. (Box 28)
  - U.S. Industrial Chemical Co. -and- Local 11-509 OCAWIU, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - United States Rubber Co. -and- Summit City Lodge 1719. I.A.M., 1956 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Rubber Co. (Ft. Wayne, Ind.) -and- Lodge 1719, IAM, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Valley Steel Casting Bay City, Mich. -and- USWA CIO Local 1877, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Vickers IUE, 1956 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Vickers, Inc. -and- Local 945, IUE General file Aug. 1959 Arb. Hear. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Vickers, Inc. -and- Local 945, IUE, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Vickers- Inc. IUE, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Vickers, Incorporated -and- Local 945 IUE, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Vickers, Incorporated -and- Local 945, IUE, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Vickers, Incorporated -and- Local 945, IUE, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Vickers, Incorporated -and- Local 945m, IUE, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Vickers, Incorporated -and- IUE, 1957 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Vickers, Incorporated -and- Local 945, IUE, 1952-1960 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Vickers, Incorporated -and- Local 945, IUE, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Vickers, Incorporated -and- Local 945, IUE, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    Photographs
  - Vickers, Incorporated -and Local 945, IUE, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Vickers, Inc. - Whirlpool Corp.. (Box 29)
  - Vickers, Inc. -and- Local 945, IUE, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Vickers, Incorporated -and- Local 945, IUE, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Vickers, Incorporated -and- Local 945, IUE, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Vickers, Incorporated -and- Local 945, IUE, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Vickers, Inc. -and- Local 945, IUE-AFL-CIO, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Vickers, Incorporated -and- Local 945, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Vindicator Printing Co. -and- Youngstown Mailers Union No. 80, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - WTAC, The Big Station, Inc. -and- NABET, AFL-CIO, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - WWJ-TV The Evening News Assn. -and- Stage Employees Local 38 AFL-CIO, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - S.D. Warren Co. -and- United Paperworkers, etc. Gr. 275 Herman Puckett William Ball., 1960 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Wayne Pump Company U.E., Local 903, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - West Mich. Dock and Market Corp. -and- Local 1608 International Brotherhood of Longshoremen, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Mr. Alexander, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Misc., 1957-1960 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Whirlpool Corporation -and- Local 1918, International Association of Machinists, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Whirlpool Corp. -and- Local 1918 International Association of Machinists, AFL-CIO, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Whirlpool Corporation -and- Local 1918. International Association of Machinists, AFL-CIO, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Whirlpool Corp. St. Joseph, Mich. -and- Local Lodge 1918, International Assn. of Machinists, AFL-CIO, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- White Pine Copper Co. - Wyandotte Chemicals Co.. (Box 30)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America Dist. 33, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America Dist. 33 Gr. 445, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America Dist. 33 Gr. 448, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America Dist. 33 Gr. 449 and 458, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America Dist. 33 Gr. 454, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America Dist. 33 Gr 455, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America District 33 Gr. 461, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America Dist. 33 Gr. 447, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America Dist. 33 Gr. 473, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America Dist. 33 Gr. 469, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America Dist. 33 Gr. 471, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1967 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America Gr. 820, 825, 828, 832, 839, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America Gr. 939, 1969 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America Gr. 996, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America Gr. 965, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - White Pine Copper Co. -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 1002, UAW, AFL-CIO (Middleville- Gr. Rapids, Mich.), 1957 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Whitehead + Kales ADD USWA - CIO, 1955 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Wyandotte Southern R.R. Co. -and- Local 12100, UMW of Amer. Dist. 50, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Wyandotte Chemicals Corp. -and- Local 12270, Dist. 50 UMWA, 1956 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Wyandatte Chemicals - UMW Riggers vs. Pipefitters, 1954 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Wyandotte Chemicals - UMW Local 12220, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Wyandotte Chemicals Corp., 1954 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Wyandotte Chemicals Co. -and- Local 11-627, OCAWIU-AFL-CIO, 1962 (Box 30, Folder 35)
- AMCAR Div. of ACF Industries -and- United Steelworkers Case MA71-2, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- AMCAR Div. of ACF Industries -and- United Steelworkers MA70-72, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Buffalo Tank Division Bethlehem Steel -and- Boilermakers - Local 169, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Clark Equipment Company -and- Local 3672, United Steelworkers AFL-CIO Case No. 72-79, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Dayton Power and Light Company -and- UWUA, AFL-CIO Local 175 Gr. 854, 1971-1972 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- City of Detroit -and- D.P.O.A., 1972 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Detroit Police Department and D.P.O.A., 1972 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Diamond Reo Trucks -and- UAW Gr. 9413, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Eltec Corporation -and- UAW Gr. BH-9301, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- General Motors Corporation Chevrolet Motor Division -and- Pattern Makers League of North America, 1971 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Inland Division of G.M. and URW, 87, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Gen Motors Inland / UMW, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Gen Motors Inland / UMW Local 87, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- GM Truck and Coach Div. -and- United Plant Guard Workers of America, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- General Tire and Rubber Company -and- United Furniture Workers, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Granite City Steel Company -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 16, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Granite City Steel Company -and- United Steelworkers of America Local 67, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Granite City Steel Company -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Granite City Steel Company -and- United Steelworkers of America, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Holly Spring Company -and- U.A.W., 1972 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Robert Hunter -and- City of Ann Arbor, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Exhibits - Hunter vs. Ann Arbor, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Robert H. Hunter -and- The City of Ann Arbor, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Hurley Hospital -and- Local 1603 AFSCME, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Hurley Hospital -and- Local 1603 AFSCME, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Inmont Corporation -and- Cincinnati Ink workers Local 1, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Inmont Corporation -and- United Automobile Workers Grievance. 77, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Inmont Corporation -and- United Automobile Workers Local 942, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Indiana and Mich. Elec. Co. -and- I.A.M.A.W., 1971 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Lake Shore, Inc. -and- Local 3168 and 3111 United Steelworkers of America, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- City of Miami -and- International Assoc. of Fire Fighters, Local 587, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Motor Wheel Corporation -and- Local 182, AIW-AFL-CIO, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Neway Division, LSI and UAW Local 1703 Gr. John Umlor, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Oakland County Sheriff Dept. -and- Metro Council 23 AFSC and ME, AFL-CIO, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Pennsylvania Power Co and UDWA Grievance 3-3-71, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Phoenix Closures, Inc. and Local 190 E.E. - Case 51-30-0219-72W (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Prudential Ins. Co. and Ins. Workers Int. AAA Case 71-30-0147-71, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Riverview School Dist. And AFSCME Grievance L-7, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Swift and Co. (Van Wagemen and Schick-Haus Co.) and Local 479 Truck drivers and Chaffeurs, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- True Temper Corp. and USW, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- U.S. Steel Corp. - South Works and Salaried Employees Assoc., 1972 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Warren Consolidated Schools and AFSCME, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Wisconsin Public Services Corp., 1972 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Bendix Corporation -and- UAW, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Bendix Corp -and- U.P.G.W. Gr. 47, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Bendix Corp -and- U.P.G.W. Gr. 45, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Bendix Corp -and- U.P.G.W. Gr. 70, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Bendix Corp -and- General File, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Bendix Corp -and- U.P.G.W. Gr. 58, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Bendix Corp -and- U.P.G.W. Gr. 62+63, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Bendix Corp -and- U.P.G.W. Gr. 65, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Bendix Corp -and- U.P.G.W. Gr. 70, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Bendix Corp -and- U.P.G.W. Gr. 216, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Bendix Corp -and- U.P.G.W. Gr. 61, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Bendix Corp -and- U.P.G.W. Gr., 1970 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Caterpillar Tractor Co. -and- Local 974, UAW-AFL-CIO, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Caterpillar Tractor Co. -and- Local 974, UAW-AFL-CIO, 1962-1966 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Caterpillar Tractor Co. -and- Local 974, UAW-AFL-CIO, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Caterpillar Tractor Co. -and- Local 974, UAW-AFL-CIO, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Caterpillar Tractor Co. -and- Local 974, UAW-AFL-CIO, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Caterpillar Tractor Co. -and- Local 974, UAW-AFL-CIO, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Caterpillar Tractor Co. -and- Local 974, UAW-AFL-CIO, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Caterpillar Tractor Co. -and- Local 974, UAW-AFL-CIO, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Caterpillar Tractor Co. -and- Local 974, UAW-AFL-CIO, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Caterpillar Tractor Co. -and- Local 974, UAW-AFL-CIO, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Caterpillar Tractor Co. -and- Local 974, UAW-AFL-CIO, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Midwest Steel Corporation and UAW, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Midwest Steel Div. -and- United Steelworkers of America, Local 6103 Grievance Nos. I-71-3001, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Midwest Steel -and- USW Gr. 67-6002, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Midwest Steel -and- USW Gr. 2-70-1052, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Midwest Steel -and- USW Gr. 2-64-1039, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Midwest Steel -and- USW 3-69-2028, 1969-1971 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Midwest Steel -and- USW Gr. 3-70-1037, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Midwest Steel Div. National Steel Corp. -and- USW Local 6103 Gr. I-70-2016, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Midwest Steel Co. Div. National Steel Corp. -and- USW Local 6103, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Consumers Power Co. (Jackson) M.S.U.W. etc. AFL-CIO, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Consumers Power Co., 1963 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Consumers Power Co., 1963 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Consumers Power Co., 1963 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Consumers Power Co., 1963 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Consumer Power Co., 1963 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Consumer Power Co., 1964 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Consumers Power Co., 1965 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Dayton Rubber Co. and United Rubber, Etc. (Local 178 - Dayton), 1956 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Dayton Rubber Co. and United Rubber, Etc. (Local 178 - Dayton), 1956 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- The Gardner Board and Carton Co. -and- United Paper workers of America, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Gerity-Mich. Corp. United Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, 1948 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Gerity-Mich. Corp. United Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers, 1947 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Swift and Co. (St. Paul) UPWA, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Swift and Co. (St. Paul) UPWA, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Swift and Co. (Des Moines) UPFAW, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Swift and Co. (Des Moines) UPFAW, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Swift and Co. (Des Moines) UPFAW, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Swift and Co. -and- (Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of N.A., 1966 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Swift and Co. (K.C.) National Bro. of Packinghouse Workers, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Swift and Co. Local 1406 Int. Assoc. Mach. And Aero. Workers, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Swift and Co. AMCBW, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Swift and Co. - St. Paul -Norfolk, Va. Processing Sales Unit, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Swift and Co. (UPWA) (St. Paul), 1961 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Swift and Co. International Brotherhood., Teams (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Swift and Co. UPW - Springfield, Mass., 1960 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Swift and Co. (S. St. Joseph, Mo.) NPWA, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Swift and Co. (Clinton, Iowa) UPFAW, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Swift and Co. (Des Moines) UPFAW, 1965 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Swift and Co. (St. Jos., Mo.) NBPW, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- American and National Leagues of Professional Baseball Clubs -and- Major League Baseball Players Association Case 72-3, 1972-1974 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- American and National Leagues of Professional Baseball Clubs -and- Major League Baseball Players Association Case 72-2, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- American and National Leagues of Professional Baseball Clubs -and- Major League Baseball Players Association Case 72-16, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- American and National Leagues of Professional Baseball Clubs -and- Major League Baseball Players Association Case 73-8, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 4)